<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Insights on Pragmatic DLT</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Insights on Pragmatic DLT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to choose blockchain development company?</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/top-blockchain-dev-company/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/top-blockchain-dev-company/</guid>
      <description>How to choose blockchain development company? When it comes to selecting a blockchain development company, there are several important factors to consider. In the world of Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs), it is crucial to find a company that has the experience and expertise to develop NFT-based solutions, such as NFT minting websites, NFT marketplace platforms, NFT auction platforms, and NFT app development.
One of the most important things to consider when selecting a blockchain development company is recognition and feedback.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User Interface for marketplace</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/nft-user-interface/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/nft-user-interface/</guid>
      <description>What NFT Marketplace is and is ReactJS a good technology for it? NFT (non-fungible tokens) is a digital asset that represents ownership of unique assets like digital art, music, and real estate. NFTs have been gaining popularity in recent years, particularly in the metaverse, where they play an important role in the virtual world&amp;rsquo;s economy. NFTs are stored on a blockchain, which ensures their scarcity and uniqueness, making them valuable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NFT Marketplace tech stack</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/nft-stack-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/nft-marketplace/nft-stack-index/</guid>
      <description>What NFT Marketplace is and is ReactJS a good technology for it? What NFT Marketplace is and is ReactJS a good technology for it? NFTs or Non-Fungible Tokens are digital assets that are unique and cannot be duplicated or divided. They are stored on a blockchain network, making them tamper-proof and providing their owners with a proof of ownership. NFTs are becoming increasingly popular in the world of art, collectibles, real estate, and more, making NFT marketplaces a rapidly growing industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clear Communication and Dynamic Agile Methodology Makes Pragmatic DLT Stand out Exclusively at GoodFirms</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Focusing on providing helpful, transparent advice and high-quality Blockchain solutions to the clients in different geographies facilitates Pragmatic DLT as the top Blockchain solutions provider in Canada at GoodFirms.
View the Pragmatic DLT&amp;rsquo;s GoodFirms&amp;rsquo; profile to get the insights of the company and its way of crafting and catering solutions to global clients.
About Pragmatic DLT Rich in providing to the clients with the best possible solutions in Blockchain technology, Pragmatic DLT founded in 2018 is headquartered in Canada.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pragmatic DLT Makes Exclusive Clutch Leaders List</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/clutchleader/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/clutchleader/</guid>
      <description>Pragmatic DLT Makes Exclusive Clutch Leaders List for Canada Developers! As an innovative software development company with a focus on technical consulting and the fintech industry, we believe that the world economy is undergoing a shift caused by megatrends, particularly decentralization. Over this past year, we’ve specialized in fintech business consulting and quickly launch the proof of concept blockchain solutions and scale them as quickly as possible. Our success has not gone unnoticed, as Pragmatic DLT has recently been recognized by among the leading blockchain companies in Canada on Clutch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup private Ethereum network in cloud</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/setup_ethereum/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/setup_ethereum/</guid>
      <description>Setup private Ethereum network in cloud This insight is a step by step guide how to launch private Ethereum network. It is a great starting point to start experiments and play with different setup and configuration options for your specific needs (block creation time, number of nodes per availability zone, block target gas limit, etc&amp;hellip;).
Private chain A private chain can potentially have huge advantages over public - level of control we get is much higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to hire blockchain team</title>
      <link>http://example.org/insights/howto-hire-blockshain-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/insights/howto-hire-blockshain-team/</guid>
      <description>How to hire team of blockchain developers Tina and her team did an ICO in May. They hit the hard cap of $12m and celebrated success, taking a few weeks&amp;rsquo; break from the rush. After the dust settled and founders&amp;rsquo; LinkedIn cooled down from the overwhelming flow of &amp;lsquo;kudos&amp;rsquo; and business offers, the team sat in the office to plan the next steps.
One thing became obvious - they are not set to build a product.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
